ADEYEMI RACHEAL OYINDAMOLA

25, Akinrinade street, Oke Aro, Ogun State

Email:rachealadeyemi.net@gmail.com Tel:+2348130692014 Linkedin: https://linkedin.com/in/adeyemi-racheal-0763aa192

PROFILE

I am an experienced web and mobile application developer with 4 years of frontend web development experience and a passion for creating picture-perfect, interactive, aesthetically pleasing, and mobile responsive web designs. Skilled in using a wide range of technologies and tools to implement core frontend development tasks such as web and mobile site design, responsive web and mobile app development, website maintenance, styling support, 3rd party API integration, and so on. Capable of developing and executing strategies to complete key project deliverables and provide compelling business value to clients and employers.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Operating System: Windows, Linux, Unix

Version Control: Git

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, Dart

Frameworks and Libraries: JQuery, SaaS, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, ReactJS,

VueJS, NuxtJS, Flutter

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Developer

2022 –present

The Kredi Bank, Anjouse Lekki Phase 1, Lagos State

- Designed and developed responsive and user-friendly web interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, including designers, developers, and project managers, to deliver high-quality projects on time and within budget.
- Developed and maintained code libraries, ensuring consistency in design and functionality across projects.
- Conducted thorough testing and debugging to identify and resolve issues and improve the overall user experience.
- Stayed up-to-date with the latest industry trends and technologies to ensure optimal performance and user experience.

Frontend Developer

2022

The Federal Polytechnic Ilaro, Ogun State

• Designed and developed user-friendly and visually appealing web interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

- Worked collaboratively with other developers, designers, and project managers to deliver high-quality projects within project timelines and budgets.
- Conducted extensive testing and debugging to identify and resolve issues and improve the overall user experience.
- Maintained and updated code libraries, ensuring consistency in design and functionality across projects.
- Demonstrated excellent communication and problem-solving skills to provide effective solutions to complex problems.

Frontend Web Developer and Mobile App Developer

2020 - 2022

Zealarax Technologies

- Designed a responsive and adaptive User interface
- Provide state management system on every application developed and consumption of Rest API.
- Perform extensive code optimization and testing of the application.
- Deployed application on play store and google store after successful testing.

Frontend Web Developer (Intern)

2017 - 2021

Zealarax Technologies

- Deliver engaging user experience through optimization of images, code, and cross-browser compatibility
- Designed dynamic and browser-compatible pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Expand features, refine code and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Computer Science

2019 - 2021

The Federal Polytechnic, Ilaro

HND - Distinction

Computer Science

2016 - 2018

The Federal Polytechnic, Ilaro

OND- Distinction

PROJECTS

Kiakia Payments - A digital bank

Role: Frontend Developer

University of Abuja - School Website

Role: Frontend Developer

Federal Polytechnic Ilaro - School Website

Role: Frontend Developer

Gospel Unites - Christian Media streaming platform

Role: Mobile Application Developer **FPI SOS** - Emergency Alert Application Role: Mobile Application Developer

CERTIFICATES AND LICENSE

- Flutter and Dart course complete Guide
- Introduction to User Experience Design

VOLUNTEERS

Programmers' Hub 2021

Role: Vice-President and Frontend Team Lead

The Federal polytechnic, Ilaro

Nigeria Association of Computing Students (NACOS) 2021

Role: Vice-President

The Federal polytechnic, Ilaro

She Codes Africa 2022

Role: Member Abeokuta Chapter